let questions = [
    {   // QUESTION #1
        question: "How many people were on the commitee to write the Declaration of Independence?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "1",
        choiceB: "2",
        choiceC: "3",
        choiceD: "5",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #2
        question: "When did congress officialy vote to declare independence from Britain?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "July 1st, 1776",
        choiceB: "July 2nd, 1776",
        choiceC: "July 3rd, 1776",
        choiceD: "July 4th, 1776",
        correct: "B"
    },
    {   // QUESTION #3
        question: "What are the first words of the Delcaration of Independence?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "We hold these truths to be self-evident",
        choiceB: "We the People of the United States...",
        choiceC: "When in the Course of human events...",
        choiceD: "In the early ages of the world...",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #4
        question: "In the New York campaign, Americans built 2 forts named Fort Washington and ____",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Fort Lee",
        choiceB: "Fort Arnold",
        choiceC: "Fort Necessity",
        choiceD: "Fort Moultrie",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #5
        question: "South of Brooklyn, the Americans forgot to cover a pass named:",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Cuban Pass",
        choiceB: "Jamaica Pass",
        choiceC: "Season Pass",
        choiceD: "Trenton Pass",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #6
        question: "South of Brooklyn, an strong retreat was organized by ____",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Benedict Arnold",
        choiceB: "Lafayette",
        choiceC: "James Grant",
        choiceD: "William Alexander",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #7
        question: "What title did William Alexander go by?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Baron von Steuben",
        choiceB: "Prince William",
        choiceC: "Lord Stirling",
        choiceD: "Marquis de Lafayette",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #8
        question: "Who won the battle of Long Island?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Washington's army",
        choiceB: "Howe's army",
        choiceC: "Tie",
        choiceD: "Both sides fled",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #9
        question: "In the New York campaign, which foreign group of mercenaries were fighting under the British?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Hessians",
        choiceB: "Russians",
        choiceC: "Italians",
        choiceD: "Dutch",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #10
        question: "Bonus Question! What type of wood was Fort Moultrie in Charleston made out of?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Cork oak",
        choiceB: "Eucalyptus wood",
        choiceC: "Palmetto wood",
        choiceD: "Ironwood",
        correct: "C"
    }
];